

SUMMARY

I'm a software engineer specializing in frontend development. I love building user-friendly, visually appealing applications with a strong focus on performance. I'm passionate about learning, staying up to date with industry trends, and researching user needs to design and implement complete solutions.

My goal is to contribute to the development of applications that meet or exceed expectations through collaboration with talented teams.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer, Helmi

March 2024 - Current

At Helmi, I'm responsible for designing and implementing everything at the frontend level, working closely with the product and backend teams to ensure a seamless experience, always prioritizing user satisfaction.

Node - React - Tailwind

Web Developer, web3tales

May 2023 - Feb 2024

Spearheaded the development of a full-stack Next.js web application. Led efforts in creating a highly responsive and visually appealing web app, prioritizing branding and employing cutting-edge SEO techniques.

Nextjs - React - Tailwind

EDUCATION

Buenos Aires Technological Institute (ITBA)

2019 - Current

Software Engineering

School of Secondary Technical Education N°7 (IMPA)

Avionics Technician

2012 - 2018

PROYECTS

Scheduler Frontend

2022 - 2023

A webpage designed to assist ITBA students to organize their academic terms by selecting completed subjects and presenting all possible course combinations.

Svelte

Wavam Frontend

March - July 2022

Podcast webpage oriented to centralize all podcast in one place with a search system, recommendations and user management.

React

CONTACT

(+54) 1121551235



abenve.dev@gmail.com



github.com/aBenve

in linkedin.com/in/abenve

PORTFOLIO

<u>abenve.com</u>

SKILLS

- Typescript
- Node
- Next
- GIT
- React
- CSS
- Tailwind
- Figma
- Python
- PostgreSQL

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (native)
- English (intermediate)

